(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-09T18:32:57.949594",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
I look above, the stars are bright,
Yet I'm blinded by your light,
Heaven seems so far away,
Come back to me someday.
The skies seem so blue,
They lead me to you,
Somewhere there's a place in my heart,
In the skies of love.
波打ち際 ほどけた髪 帽子の先
Flowing locks on the shore, beyond the hat's brim
見覚えある青いワーゲン stop the flashback
A familiar blue Wagen, stop the flashback
南風の いたずらな魔法ね
In southern winds, a playful magic
遠い夏のあの眩暈に戻さないで be with you again
Don't send me back to that dizzy summer, be with you again
maybe love, stray my heart
なに食わぬ顔をして
With a casual look on my face
キスを奪って don't go away
Stealing a kiss, don't go away
今だけは寄り添ってあげるわ
For now, I'll lean close to you
唇にぬくもり残して close to you
Leaving warmth on my lips, close to you
肩すくめてボネットから腰上げて
Shrugging my shoulders and lifting off the bonnet
語りすぎて飽きてきたわ stay the flashlight
Tired of talking too much, stay the flashlight
似た人みたい 解きかけた魔法ね
Like someone I know, the magic is fading out
遠い夏のあの眩暈に戻りたいの no more
I want to return to those dizzy summer days, no more
maybe love, stray my heart
さりげないしぐさして
With a casual brush-off
キスをそらすわ i go away
I turn away the kiss and go away
夕立に付き合う気ないから
Not in the mood to weather the rain with you
崩れてくオンショア 波のまにまに turnaround
Crumbling onshore waves, turning around with the tide
maybe love, stray my heart
何もかも蜃気楼
It's all a mirage
夏の女神の気まぐれね
Just the whim of the summer goddess
いつかまただなんて i never say
Saying see you again someday, I never say
唇にうはら残したままで turnaround
Leaving a lingering lie on my lips, turnaround
肩すくめて ボンネットから 腰上げて
Shrugging my shoulders, lifting my hips off the hood,
喋りすぎよ 飽きてきたわ stay the flashlight
Talking too much, getting tired, stay the flashlight,
似た人みたい そうルックアライク
Looking like someone, looking alike,
謎解きかけた魔法ね fade-in fade-out
The unraveling magic, fade-in fade-out.
遠い夏のあの眩暈に 戻りたいの be with you again
I want to return to that distant summer dizziness, be with you again.
maybe love, stray my heart
さりげないしぐさして キズをそらすわ i go away
With a casual gesture, I'll deflect the wound, I go away.
夕立に付き合う気はないから...
I don't feel like sticking around for the evening shower...
崩れてくオンショア 波のまにまに turnaround
The onshore crumbles, at the mercy of the waves, turnaround.
maybe love, stray my heart 何もかも蜃気楼
Maybe love, stray my heart, everything is a mirage.
夏の女神の気まぐれね
The whims of the summer goddess,
いつかまただなんて i never say
Someday I'll say "never again," i never say.
唇にうはらは残したままで turnaround
Leaving lingering feelings on my lips, turnaround.
波打ち際 ほぐれた髪 帽子 の先
At the water's edge, untied hair, the tip of a hat,
見覚えある 青いワーゲン stop the flashback
A familiar blue Volkswagen, stop the flashback.
南風のいたずらね it's magic rays
Mischief of the southern wind, it's magic rays.
遠い夏のあの眩暈に 戻りたくないの be with you no more
I don't want to return to that distant summer dizziness, be with you no more.
maybe love, stray my heart
さりげないしぐさして キズをそらすわ i go away
With a casual gesture, I'll deflect the wound, i go away.
夕立に付き合う気はないから...
I don't feel like sticking around for the evening shower...
崩れてくオンショア 波のまにまに turnaround
The onshore crumbles, at the mercy of the waves, turnaround.
maybe love, stray my heart
何もかも蜃気楼
Everything is a mirage,
夏の女神の気まぐれね
The whims of the summer goddess,
いつかまただなんて i never say
Someday I'll say "never again," i never say.
唇にうはらは残したままで turnaround
Leaving lingering feelings on my lips, turnaround.
肩すくめて ボンネットから 腰上げて
Shrugging my shoulders, lifting my hips off the hood,
喋りすぎよ 飽きてきたわ stay the flashlight
Talking too much, getting tired, stay the flashlight,
似た人みたい そうルックアライク
Looking like someone, looking alike,
謎解きかけた魔法ね fade-in fade-out
The unraveling magic, fade-in fade-out.
遠い夏のあの眩暈に 戻りたいの be with you again
I want to return to that distant summer dizziness, be with you again.
maybe love, stray my heart
さりげないしぐさして キズをそらすわ i go away
With a casual gesture, I'll deflect the wound, i go away.
夕立に付き合う気はないから...
I don't feel like sticking around for the evening shower...
崩れてくオンショア 波のまにまに turnaround
The onshore crumbles, at the mercy of the waves, turnaround.
maybe love, stray my heart
何もかも蜃気楼
Everything is a mirage,
夏の女神の気まぐれね
The whims of the summer goddess,
いつかまただなんて i never say
Someday I'll say "never again," i never say.
唇にうはらは残したままで turnaround
Leaving lingering feelings on my lips, turnaround.
ANGEL
[Song: ANGEL]
見つけるのに 貝殻探して ふた手で迷い
Searching for shells, hesitating in two directions,
あす雪の フェリーに合わすと 本気で寝る
Wondering if we'll catch tomorrow's snow ferry, I sleep deeply.
風邪と青い 夏の片隅 砂の白さは 過ぎたロマン
A cold wind, a blue summer corner, white sand is a bygone romance.
甘いささやき 心をくすぐるよ
Sweet whispers tickle my heart,
嫌なら あんまり濡れたら 唇を拭き ただ思い出す もういい
If you don't like it, don't get too wet, wipe your lips and just remember, that's enough.
もう夏の片隅 砂の白さは 過ぎたロマン
Already a corner of summer, white sand is a bygone romance,
甘いささやき 心をくすぐるよ 落ちるのか
Sweet whispers tickle my heart, will it fall?
いやなら あんまり濡れたら 唇を拭き ただ思い出す もういい
If you don't like it, don't get too wet, wipe your lips and just remember, that's enough.
ヘンチェン It's time the smile is on my way
Change, it's time the smile is on my way,
決めることの 終わりに誰もが ひとりでに
At the end of making decisions, everyone naturally...
終わるのよ
...comes to an end.
ヘンチェン It's time the smile is on my way
Change, it's time the smile is on my way,
決めることの 終わりに誰もが
At the end of making decisions, everyone...
ひとりでに
...all alone...
終わるのよ 誰もが ひとりでに
Ends, everyone all by themselves...
Ends, everyone all by themselves.
STOP 星屑で髪を飾り
STOP Adorning my hair with stardust
NON-STOP 優しい瞳を待つわ プールサイド
NON-STOP Waiting for your kind eyes at the poolside
STOP 星屑で髪を飾り
STOP Adorning my hair with stardust
NON-STOP 優しい瞳を待つわ プールサイド
NON-STOP Waiting for your kind eyes at the poolside
好き、好き 切なく ふるえる胸
Liked, liked, my chest trembling with anguish
幻でもいい 逢いたいのに
Even if it's an illusion, I want to meet you
Heart on wave Heart on wave あなたは来ない
Heart on wave Heart on wave You don't come
私の思いをジョークにしないで
Don't make a joke out of my feelings
Lonely ユラユラ swimmin' ユラユラ dream in'
Lonely Swaying, swaying swimmin' Swaying, swaying dream in'
愛が揺れる STOP STOP STOP
Love is swaying STOP STOP STOP
LOVE 花柄の水着だけが
LOVE Only a floral swimsuit
Love me 目立ちすぎて泣きたくなるの
Love me It stands out too much and makes me want to cry
じりじり 焦げている この痛みを抱きしめ
This burning, sizzling pain, holding it close
冷たい 水辺に そっと 浮かべて
Gently floating on the cold waterside
Heart on wave Heart on wave 泳ぎ出す だけど
Heart on wave Heart on wave I start to swim, but
あなたのゆめには 追いかけられなくて
I can't catch up to your dreams
I can't ねえ こんなに 苦しいのに
I can't Hey, even though it's so painful
なぜ なぜ あなたじゃなくちゃ ダメなの
Why, why must it be you?
Lonely ユラユラ swimmin' ユラユラ dream in'
Lonely Swaying, swaying swimmin' Swaying, swaying dream in'
愛が揺れる STOP STOP STOP
Love is swaying STOP STOP STOP
Heart on wave Heart on wave あなたは来ない
Heart on wave Heart on wave You don't come
私の思いをジョークにしないで
Don't make a joke out of my feelings
Heart on wave Heart on wave 泳ぎ出すけれど
Heart on wave Heart on wave I start to swim, but
あなたのゆめには 追いかけられなくて
I can't catch up to your dreams
STOP 星屑で髪を飾り
STOP Adorning my hair with stardust
NON-STOP 優しい瞳を待つわ プールサイド
NON-STOP Waiting for your kind eyes at the poolside
好き、好き 切なく ふるえる胸
Liked, liked, my chest trembling with anguish
幻でもいい 逢いたいのに
Even if it's an illusion, I want to meet you
Heart on wave Heart on wave あなたは来ない
Heart on wave Heart on wave You don't come
私の思いをジョークにしないで
Don't make a joke out of my feelings
Lonely ユラユラ swimmin' ユラユラ dream in'
Lonely Swaying, swaying swimmin' Swaying, swaying dream in'
愛が揺れる STOP STOP STOP
Love is swaying STOP STOP STOP
LOVE 花柄の水着だけが
LOVE Only a floral swimsuit
Love me 目立ちすぎて泣きたくなるの
Love me It stands out too much and makes me want to cry
じりじり 焦げている この痛みを抱きしめ
This burning, sizzling pain, holding it close
冷たい 水辺に そっと 浮かべて
Gently floating on the cold waterside
淋しい熱帯魚
[Title: Lonely Tropical Fish]
STOP 星屑で髪を飾り
STOP Adorning my hair with stardust
NON-STOP 優しい瞳を待つわ プールサイド
NON-STOP Waiting for your kind eyes at the poolside
好き、好き 切なく ふるえる胸
Liked, liked, my chest trembling with anguish
幻でもいい 逢いたいのに
Even if it's an illusion, I want to meet you
Heart on wave Heart on wave あなたは来ない
Heart on wave Heart on wave You don't come
私の思いをジョークにしないで
Don't make a joke out of my feelings
Lonely ユラユラ swimmin' ユラユラ dream in'
Lonely Swaying, swaying swimmin' Swaying, swaying dream in'
愛が揺れる STOP STOP STOP
Love is swaying STOP STOP STOP
LOVE 花柄の水着だけが
LOVE Only a floral swimsuit
Love me 目立ちすぎて泣きたくなるの
Love me It stands out too much and makes me want to cry
じりじり 焦げている この痛みを抱きしめ
This burning, sizzling pain, holding it close
冷たい 水辺に そっと 浮かべて
Gently floating on the cold waterside
Heart on wave Heart on wave 泳ぎ出す だけど
Heart on wave Heart on wave I start to swim, but
Darling 朝までいたい
Darling, I want to stay with you until morning
Darling 愛感じたい
Darling, I want to feel your love
Darling 素肌のまま二人
Darling, bare-skinned, just the two of us
Wow wow wow wow
Darling 波の音さえ
Darling, even the sound of the waves
Darling 息苦しいの
Darling, it's suffocating
Darling 思い切り抱いてよ
Darling, hold me tight
Wow wow wow wow wow
パーティ抜け出す チャンスつかんで
Sneaking out of the party, seizing the chance,
今 月明り 砂浜に揺れる
tonight, the moonlight sways on the sandy beach.
私的のハート あなたが好き
My private heart—I love you.
噂ふりまいて あなたをその気にさせたいの
Spreading rumors, I want to make you fall for me.
そうよ Darling 夜間抜け出した
That's right. Darling, we slipped out into the night.
Darling 二人はきっと
Darling, we're sure.
Darling すべてが変わってる
Darling, everything is changing.
Wow wow wow wow wow
あなたの理想のタイプじゃないと知ってても
Even though I know I'm not your ideal type,
体でぶつかる私を見れば感じるはず
if you see me clashing with all my might, you're bound to feel it.
今まで他の女に見せないあなたを私だけに見せて
Show me the side of you you've never shown to other girls, show it only to me.
Darling 朝までいたい
Darling, I want to stay with you until morning,
Darling 愛感じたい
Darling, I want to feel your love.
Darling 素肌のまま二人
Darling, bare-skinned, just the two of us.
Wow wow wow wow
Darling 波の音さえ
Darling, even the sound of the waves,
Darling 息苦しいの
Darling, it's suffocating.
Darling 思い切り抱いてよ
Darling, hold me tight.
Wow wow wow wow wow
好きよ
I love you.
Darling 朝までいたい
Darling, I want to stay with you until morning,
Darling 愛感じたい
Darling, I want to feel your love.
Darling 素肌のまま二人
Darling, bare-skinned, just the two of us.
Wow wow wow wow
Darling 夜間抜け出した
Darling, we slipped out into the night.
Darling 二人はきっと
Darling, we're sure.
Darling すべてが変わってる
Darling, everything is changing.
Wow wow wow wow wow
好きよ
I love you.
テレフォン・ナンバー
[Song: Telephone Number]
Ah-uuh... 56709
忘れないで 私の テレフォン・ナンバー
Don't forget my telephone number.
困った時 ダイアルして欲しい、いつでも
When you're in trouble, I want you to dial it, anytime.
そう every night 飲み続けている あなたの寂しさに、気づいていた
Yes, every night, I've noticed your loneliness as you keep drinking.
Oh... loving you
Ah-uuh... 56709
背の高い あなたが 小さく見えるから
Because you, who are so tall, look so small
旅立つ朝 笑顔で 行って欲しい、お願い
on the morning you set off—I want you to go with a smile, please.
そう every day, ベルを気にしては 暮らすわ この愛に、気付いたら
Yes, every day, I live worrying about the bell—if you realize this love,
Oh... loving me
Ah-uuh... 56709
あうー……
Ah, ooooh...
忘れないで、私のテレフォン・ナンバー、
Don't forget my telephone number,
困った時ダイヤルして欲しい、いつまでも。
I want you to dial whenever you're in trouble, always.
そうevery night
Yes, every night
飲み続けているあなたの、
You keep drinking,
寂しさに（あ！）、
Your loneliness, ah!
気づいてた（あ！）、
I noticed, ah!
oh, oh loving you
あうー……
Ah, ooooh...
背の高いあなたが小さく見えるから、
You're tall, but you look small to me,
旅立つ朝 笑顔で行って欲しい お願い。
On the morning you leave, go with a smile, please.
そうevery day、
Yes, every day,
ベルを気にしてみは暮らすわ、
I live worrying about the bell ringing,
この愛に（あ！）、
This love, ah!
気づいたら（あ！）、
When you realize, ah!
oh - oh loving me
あうー……
Ah, ooooh...
YOUTHFUL DAYS' GRAFFITI
[Title: YOUTHFUL DAYS' GRAFFITI]
Upside down endless nights
Upside down over the lights
揺れる景色 心模様を
Swaying scenery, feelings in my heart
響く言葉 奏で合おう
Resonating words, let's play them together
たゆとう見界 世界を探して
Searching for a drifting, wavering world
カウントダウン yeah, yeah, yeah
Countdown yeah, yeah, yeah
wow, wow
片道道路の 切れ端とぼう
Let's wander to the edge of a one-way road
語らうからがきっと
Surely because we talk together
Upside down endless nights
今夜は眠らずに
Without sleeping tonight
Upside down endless nights
リズムに乗せちゃえば
If we ride on the rhythm
跳ねるビート 乙女心 辿る奇跡
Bouncing beats, a maiden's heart tracing miracles
試される刺激 炎を燃やしてバニラ
Tested stimulation, burning flames of vanilla
upside-down endless rise
upside-down overdrive
揺れる 景色 心 模様
Shaking scenery and shifting hearts,
響く 言葉 in other world
Echoing words in another world.
漂う 魅惑 世界 を
Drifting through an enchanting realm,
急か し て
hurrying it along,
count down yeah yeah
wow～ 片言 の 切れ端 と
Woah~ With fragments of broken words,
wow～ 語る 身体 と
Woah~ And a body that speaks.
upside-down take me tonight
今宵 は 眠ら ず に
we won't sleep at all tonight.
upside-down midnight delight
踊り 明かそうよ
let's dance until the morning.
upside-down endless rise
リズム に 乗せ ちゃえば
if you ride the rhythm,
upside-down overdrive
心 も 弾む
even your heart will bound.
跳ねる 微熱 乙女 心
Bouncing slight fever, maiden heart,
辿る 軌跡 in seventeen
tracing tracks in seventeen.
彷徨う 刺激 炎 に 任せて
Yielding to the restless, burning flame,
burning love yeah yeah
wow～ 湧き上がる 本能 と
Woah~ Rising instincts,
wow～ 揺蕩う 意識 と
Woah~ And flickering consciousness.
upside-down take me tonight
路上 の ステージ で
on the stage upon the road.
upside-down midnight delight
歌い明かそうよ
let's sing all through the night.
upside-down endless rise
ビート に 委ねれば
surrendering to the beat,
upside-down overdrive
吐息 も 踊る
even our sighs dance along.
upside-down through this night
夜空 の 向こう まで
all the way past the night sky.
upside-down morning tide
タンデム で 飛ぼう
let's fly away on a tandem.
upside-down endless rise
今日 を もっと 超え ちゃえば
if we push past today even more,
upside-down overdrive
明日は good-sunshine
tomorrow brings good sunshine.
upside-down take me tonight
今宵 は 眠ら ず に
we won't sleep at all tonight.
upside-down midnight delight
踊り 明かそうよ
let's dance until the morning.
upside-down endless rise
リズム に 乗せ ちゃえば
if you ride the rhythm,
upside-down overdrive
心 も 弾む
even your heart will bound.
upside-down through this night
夜空 の 向こう まで
all the way past the night sky.
upside-down morning tide
タンデム で 飛ぼう
let's fly away on a tandem.
upside-down endless rise
今日 を もっと 超え ちゃえば
if we push past today even more,
upside-down overdrive
明日は good-sunshine
tomorrow brings good sunshine.
upside-down take me tonight
今宵 は 眠ら ず に
we won't sleep at all tonight.
upside-down midnight delight
踊り 明かそうよ
let's dance until the morning.
upside-down endless rise
リズム に 乗せ ちゃえば
if you ride the rhythm,
upside-down overdrive
心 も 弾む
even your heart will bound.
upside-down through this night
夜空 の 向こう まで
all the way past the night sky.
upside-down morning tide
タンデム で 飛ぼう
let's fly away on a tandem.
upside-down endless rise
今日 を もっと 超え ちゃえば
if we push past today even more,
upside-down overdrive
明日は good-sunshine
tomorrow brings good sunshine.
upside-down take me tonight
今宵 は 眠ら ず に
we won't sleep at all tonight.
upside-down midnight delight
踊り 明かそうよ
let's dance until the morning.
upside-down endless rise
リズム に 乗せ ちゃえば
if you ride the rhythm,
upside-down overdrive
心 も 弾む
even your heart will bound.
upside-down through this night
夜空 の 向こう まで
all the way past the night sky.
upside-down morning tide
タンデム で 飛ぼう
let's fly away on a tandem.
upside-down endless rise
今日 を もっと 超え ちゃえば
if we push past today even more,
upside-down overdrive
明日は good-sunshine
tomorrow brings good sunshine.
upside-down take me tonight
今宵 は 眠ら ず に
we won't sleep at all tonight.
upside-down midnight delight
踊り 明かそうよ
let's dance until the morning.
upside-down endless rise
リズム に 乗せ ちゃえば
if you ride the rhythm,
upside-down overdrive
心 も 弾む
even your heart will bound.
upside-down through this night
夜空 の 向こう まで
all the way past the night sky.
upside-down morning tide
タンデム で 飛ぼう
let's fly away on a tandem.
upside-down endless rise
今日 を もっと 超え ちゃえば
if we push past today even more,
upside-down overdrive
明日は good-sunshine
tomorrow brings good sunshine.
upside-down take me tonight
今宵 は 眠ら ず に
we won't sleep at all tonight.
upside-down midnight delight
踊り 明かそうよ
let's dance until the morning.
upside-down endless rise
リズム に 乗せ ちゃえば
if you ride the rhythm,
upside-down overdrive
心 も 弾む
even your heart will bound.
upside-down through this night
夜空 の 向こう まで
all the way past the night sky.
upside-down morning tide
タンデム で 飛ぼう
let's fly away on a tandem.
upside-down endless rise
今日 を もっと 超え ちゃえば
if we push past today even more,
upside-down overdrive
明日は good-sunshine
tomorrow brings good sunshine.
Plastic Love
恋のプログラムを狂わせないでね
Don't mess up the program of love
突然のキスや熱いまなざしで
with a sudden kiss or fiery stare.
出逢uと別れ上手に打ち込んで
I cleverly plan every hello and goodbye.
突然のキスや 熱いまなざしで
With your sudden kiss and fiery stare,
恋のプログラムを 狂わせないでね
don't mess up the program of love.
出逢いと別れ 上手に打ち込んで
I cleverly plan every hello and goodbye,
時間が来れば 終わる don't hurry !
because everything comes to an end, don't hurry!
愛に傷ついていた あの日からずっと
Ever since the day love hurt me,
昼と夜が逆の 暮らしを続けて
my days and nights have been reversed.
はやりの中ディスコで 踊り明かすうちに
At the flashy discotheque, dancing the night away,
おぼえた魔法なのよ i'm sorry !
it's the magic I learned, I'm sorry!
私のことを決して 本気で愛さないで
Never take loving someone like me seriously,
恋なんてただのゲーム 楽しめればそれでいいの
love is just a game, I just want to have fun.
閉ざした心を飾る 派手なドレスも靴も
I dressed up my closed heart in fancy dresses and shoes,
孤独な友達
they were my friends in loneliness.
私を誘う人は 皮肉なものね いつも
Every guy that asks me out ironically looks just like him,
彼に似てるわ なぜか思い出が重なり合う
for some reason my memories run wild.
グラスを落として 急に涙ぐんでも
Even if I drop my glass and suddenly cry,
わけは尋ねないでね
don't ask me the reason why.
夜更けの高速で 眠りにつくころ
When I fall asleep on the highway,
ハロゲンライトだけ 妖しく輝く
only the halogen lights shine mysteriously.
氷のように冷たい 女だと言わないで
Even if a voice whispers out that I'm a woman cold as ice,
don't hurry !
don't hurry!
i 'm just playing games
I'm just playing games,
i know that 's plastic love
I know that's plastic love.
dance to the plastic beat
another morning comes
私を誘う人は 皮肉なものね いつも
Every guy that asks me out ironically looks just like him,
彼に似てるわ なぜか思い出が重なり合う
for some reason my memories run wild.
グラスを落として 急に涙ぐんでも
Even if I drop my glass and suddenly cry,
わけは尋ねないでね
don't ask me the reason why.
夜更けの高速で 眠りにつくころ
When I fall asleep on the highway,
ハロゲンライトだけ 妖しく輝く
only the halogen lights shine mysteriously.
氷のように冷たい 女だと言わないで
Even if a voice whispers out that I'm a woman cold as ice,
don't hurry !
don't hurry!
夜更けの高速で 眠りにつくころ
When I fall asleep on the highway,
ハロゲンライトだけ 妖しく輝く
only the halogen lights shine mysteriously.
氷のように冷たい 女だと言わないで
Even if a voice whispers out that I'm a woman cold as ice,
don't hurry !
don't hurry!
i 'm just playing games
I'm just playing games,
i know that 's plastic love
I know that's plastic love.
dance to the plastic beat
another morning comes
i 'm just playing games
I'm just playing games,
i know that 's plastic love
I know that's plastic love.
dance to the plastic beat
another morning comes
i 'm just playing games
I'm just playing games,
i know that 's plastic love
I know that's plastic love.
dance to the plastic beat
another morning comes
i 'm just playing games
I'm just playing games,
i know that 's plastic love
I know that's plastic love.
dance to the plastic beat
another morning comes
SHYNESS BOY
[Title: SHYNESS BOY]
夏のpartyで声をかけてきたのは あなたの方からよ
You're the one that called out to me at a summer party,
いつも電話の声は ありきたりな事ばかり言ってるの
talking about ordinary things in your usual phone voice.
you are my shyness boy 待っているのよ
You are my shyness boy; I'm waiting
誘いの言葉 もどかしさなら
for those inviting words...
こっち向いてよ チェリー
Look this way, Cherry.
You are my シャイネスボーイ 待ってるのよ
You are my shyness boy, waiting for you.
誘いの言葉
Inviting words.
もどかしさなら 今日限りにして欲しい
If it's awkwardness, I want you to end it today.
I'm falling in love
夜の ドライブの後で
After a night drive,
遅いから送るよなんて
saying "It's late, I'll walk you home"
うんざりね
is so annoying.
今夜は 朝までシュート
Tonight, shooting until morning,
一緒にいられるようにしてあるの
I've made sure we can stay together.
You are my シャイネスボーイ 散々焦らせたいの
You are my shyness boy, I want to make you wait so much—
あなたの愛は
your love!
タバコ持っても 震えてる甘えた人
Even holding a cigarette, you're a trembling, spoiled person.
You are my シャイネスボーイ 待ってるのよ
You are my shyness boy, waiting for you.
決まり文句を
Customary phrases,
優しすぎるあなたの瞳 そこが好き
those eyes of yours that are too gentle—I love that about you.
You are my シャイネスボーイ 待ってるのよ
You are my shyness boy, waiting for you.
誘いの言葉
Inviting words.
もどかしさなら 今日限りにして欲しい
If it's awkwardness, I want you to end it today.
You are my シャイネスボーイ 待ってるのよ
You are my shyness boy, waiting for you.
決まり文句を
Customary phrases,
優しすぎるあなたの瞳 そこが好き
those eyes of yours that are too gentle—I love that about you.
未来派Lovers
[Title: 未来派Lovers]
君に惹かれて めためたじゃね？ 神隠し
Drawn to you, I'm a complete mess—spirited away?
ハートビートは 合わせよう それで行こうよ
Let's match our heartbeats and go with that!
キミとあたしは 未来派格好いいのテクニシャン
You and I are futuristic, cool technicians!
高く速く好き勝手に！
High, fast, however we like!
メタルボディの 肌ざわりにさえ 熱く感じてくる
Even feeling the metal body's skin texture hotly—
偶然になりそう
it seems like it'll turn into a coincidence!
チャちなイマジネーション 超えてた次元 超律違反
Petty imagination transcending dimensions, ultra law violation!
抜けるフィーリング 止めないで
A passing-through feeling, don't stop it!
君に惹かれて めためたじゃね？ 神隠し
Drawn to you, I'm a complete mess—spirited away?
ハート 繋げばスパーク 明るく ボルテージ
Connecting hearts, a spark, bright voltage!
キミとあたしは 未来派格好いいのテクニシャン
You and I are futuristic, cool technicians!
つなぎばなし 自由自在に
Connecting stories freely!
Nothing is impossible
ぐるり取り巻く 病みつき世界 軽く飛び越えてよ
Surrounding us completely, this addictive world—jump over it lightly!
新しいを連れて
Bringing something new along!
ワープも予測できない
Even warping can't be predicted
100年早い
A hundred years too early
恋人たちの I'm in love with you
Lovers' "I'm in love with you"
キミに惹かれて めためた めちゃ カグルイ
Attracted to you, totally, utterly, wildly crazy
ハートの糸はあわせろ それで行きそうよ
Align our heartstrings, let's go with that!
キミとアタシは 未来はこびのテクニシャン
You and I are technicians of carrying the future
高く 早く 好きよ 気ままに
High and fast, love freely as you please
キミに惹かれて めためた めちゃ カグルイ
Attracted to you, totally, utterly, wildly crazy
ぴったり だから やっぱ ピカイチ 切れる あるフォン好き
Perfect, after all, the top-notch sharp smartphone lover
キミとアタシは 未来はこびのテクニシャン
You and I are technicians of carrying the future
空も海も 今日も明日も
The sky and the sea, today and tomorrow too
なしりえん Possiburu!
Making the impossible possible!
Ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, jump over, Birthday Summit desuwa!
Happy Birthday to me!
Hi! How did you enjoy the live? Hello, hello!
Ooh, birthday merch time! Ooh!
This birthday features beautiful art by the ultra-talented Uchakosand!
This time inspired by the city pop genre, I got the hot rod behind me, I'm in my 80s inspired idol outfit, get and be for going cruising!
Inspired by city pop, hot rod behind, 80s idol fit, ready to cruise!
This piece also will be available as a canvas. You know what that means? Shark art appreciation time!
This piece also will be available as a canvas. Shark art appreciation time!
Also by Uchakosand, a really cool sweatshirt featuring these plans and cornerts to the ultimate shark girl!
A really cool sweatshirt featuring prints and portraits of the ultimate shark girl!
This design has so many little details. I can't decide if I want to wear mine or display it, or or buy one to wear and one to display. I don't know, but I love it so much, I think this is one of my favorite merch designs I've ever come across for myself. So, I'm really excited!
I love it so much, one of my favorite merch designs ever, so I'm really excited!
And then we have the shark keychain! You can match it with me. It's the same one I'm wearing in the canvas illustration. There's a little Ebi, and and a little Chame, and a trident, and it's blue in my favorite colors, and it's so cute!
Shark keychain! Same as the canvas. Ebi, Chame, trident, blue, so cute!
If everybody matches together, we can spot each other in the wild and then make awkward eye contact. It'll be great, right?
If everyone matches, we can spot each other and make awkward eye contact!
And finally, if you purchase the set as a bundle, it'll come with a very exclusive polaroid hand-signed by me!
Purchase as a bundle for an exclusive hand-signed Polaroid by me!
The bundle option is of course limited, so act quickly if you're interested. The links to uh the purchasing of the merchandise will be available in the description and probably alongside the the the chat hello, hello in the chat bar, yes, woohoo!
Limited bundle. Links in description and the chat bar, yes, woohoo!
Okay, I'm off to eat a very large piece of cake that does not say feet on it, totally. Ha ha. Uh not this year, maybe next year.
Eating cake that doesn't say "feet" on it. Not this year, maybe next year.
Thanks for coming to my birthday party! Yippee!
Bye bye now. Thank you. Bye-bye!
Bye-bye now. Thank you. Bye-bye!